Hi, I'm Flo and I'm eight years old.
Xin chào, mình là Flo và mình tám tuổi.
I'm in class three with my sister Ella.
Mình học lớp ba cùng chị mình Ella.
My favorite color is pink and my favorite food is mango.
Màu yêu thích của mình là hồng và món ăn yêu thích là xoài.
I like swimming and I like playing with my friend's cat.
Mình thích bơi và thích chơi với con mèo của bạn mình.
Cats are my favorite animals.
Mèo là động vật yêu thích của mình.
Hello, my name's Charlie and I'm five years old.
Xin chào, mình tên Charlie và mình năm tuổi.
I go to kindergarten.
Mình đi mẫu giáo.
My favorite color is red and my favorite food
Màu yêu thích của mình là đỏ và món ăn yêu thích
is chocolate ice cream.
là kem sô-cô-la.
I like playing basketball with my brother Luke
Mình thích chơi bóng rổ với anh trai Luke
and I like elephants.
và mình thích voi.
Hi, I'm Luke and I'm 11 years old.
Xin chào, mình là Luke và mình 11 tuổi.
I'm in class six now.
Giờ mình học lớp sáu.
My favorite color is blue.
Màu yêu thích của mình là xanh dương.
That's why I'm wearing this T-shirt.
Đó là lý do mình mặc chiếc áo phông này.
My favorite food is a burger.
Món ăn yêu thích của mình là bánh hamburger.
I like playing football and I like watching it too.
Mình thích chơi bóng đá và cũng thích xem nữa.
I like big animals.
Mình thích động vật lớn.
My favorite animal is a lion.
Động vật yêu thích của mình là sư tử.
Hello, my name's Ella and I'm eight years old.
Xin chào, mình tên Ella và mình tám tuổi.
I'm in class three with my sister Flo.
Mình học lớp ba cùng em mình Flo.
My favorite color is yellow, like my T-shirt.
Màu yêu thích của mình là vàng, giống chiếc áo phông của mình.
Grapes are my favorite food
Nho là món ăn yêu thích của mình
and I like playing tennis with my friends.
và mình thích chơi quần vợt với bạn bè.
Horses are my favorite animals.
Ngựa là động vật yêu thích của mình.